{
    "subject": "resource/TextDrive",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "Hosting",
    "human_readable": "TextDrive is in the hosting industry.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9036300182342529,
            "question": "What industry is TextDrive involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7646239399909973,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by companies in the hosting industry like TextDrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6417877078056335,
            "question": "How does TextDrive differentiate itself from other hosting companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6193950176239014,
            "question": "Are there any specific technologies or platforms that TextDrive specializes in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4878132939338684,
            "question": "Can you give examples of companies that compete with TextDrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4064297676086426,
            "question": "Who might be the target audience for TextDrive's products or services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4037284255027771,
            "question": "What type of services does TextDrive likely provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.344853937625885,
            "question": "What factors would influence a person's decision to choose TextDrive over other hosting options?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3298359811306,
            "question": "What are the potential benefits of using TextDrive's services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18230506777763367,
            "question": "How has the hosting industry evolved over time, and what trends can be observed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=TextDrive is in the hosting industry.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6726_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the potential benefits of using TextDrive's services?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6726_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors would influence a person's decision to choose TextDrive over other hosting options?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6726_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of services does TextDrive likely provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6726_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6726_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To answer your query, I will evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"TextDrive is in the hosting industry.\"\n\nAfter reviewing the context information, I found that the following sentences support this triple:\n\n* \"TextDrive is a provider of Shared Hosting services.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6726/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt)\n* \"TextDrive is a hosting company run by and for people who love publishing on the web.\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6726/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt)\n\nTherefore, based on the information in the documents, I conclude that:\n\n*output*: *yes*"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that TextDrive offers hosting services, such as shared hosting and Accelerator technology. Therefore, it supports the statement that TextDrive is in the hosting industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}